Let's change seats.
My ordinary high school life
took a turn with this seat change,
and turned completely upside down.
(I like you.)
Huh?
Is this some kind of prank?
Wait.
If that note...
Ah.
Isn't a prank?
Teacher Komori?
Wait, does that mean I'm getting
in the way of Asamiya's love life?
He's good-looking and smart.
He's one of the most
popular guys in school.
If I piss off a guy like Asamiya,
my high school life is...
What have you been doing this whole time?
Whoa!
It's him.
That note
was meant for you, Mayama.
Huh?
You're asking what I like about you?
Let's take our time finding out.
That helps a lot.
Pointing out my flaws like that.
Those aren't your flaws.
Those are the things I
like about you, Mayama.
Always putting others first,
even if it means you lose out.
That's just how sweet you are, Mayama.
I'm looking forward to getting to know you.
After Moving Seats, The Boy Behind
Me Has A Crush On Me (Episode 2)
Asamiya.
When you said you liked me,
did you mean...
you like me as a friend, right?
Which one do you think it is?
Am I dreaming right now?
(How you tend to slouch.) (How you always have bedhead.)
(How you always take the short end of the stick.)
Those are the things I
like about you, Mayama.
Since that day, Asamiya's sticky note
attacks have only gotten more intense.
At this rate, before the
first semester is even over,
my entire notebook will
be covered in sticky notes.
Did something good happen?
Huh?
It's just rare,
for you to be up this early, Hare.
I do this sometimes.
I'm heading out now.
Ah, wait.
You've got a cowlick.
Ah, this... It's fine like this.
Huh?
I'm off!
Morning.
Ah...
You really left your hair sticking up.
You said you wanted to
touch it every three days, right?
I'd touch it every day if I could.
What's that?
A thank-you for last time.
Bread?
Didn't you buy me bread
at the cafeteria before?
So I bought some at the convenience store.
Asamiya?
When I die, please put this
in my coffin with me.
Don't do that. Eat it now
before it goes bad.
Got it.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Also,
writing all those sticky notes must
be tiring. You can slow down, it's fine.
I thought I was already holding back a lot.
Huh?
Because I've barely written anything yet.
But since you mentioned it,
I'll keep it in mind.
Thanks.
Asamiya is really sweet.
I enjoy spending time with him, too.
But...
At the time, I had no idea that
becoming friends with Asamiya
would lead to another problem.
Morning!
Asamiya walking to school with someone?
That's a rare sight.
Right?
Becoming friends with Asamiya
meant I also had to deal with
these popular guys.
Did you do the homework?
- Nope.
- You look like you didn't.
I knew you definitely wouldn't.
Sakaki, did you break up again?
We just weren't a good match.
Wait a minute.
What's your longest relationship so far?
Huh? But...
Hmm... One, two, three...?
Two... three months?
More like two or three weeks.
Bingo.
It's like a conversation
from another world.
What about you, Asamiya?
Is there anyone you're
interested in right now?
Maybe.
Huh? Really?
Who is it?
Who?
I can't believe Asamiya has someone.
That's rare.
Alright, enough about me.
What about you, Sakaki? Got
your eye on someone new?
Hmm... Not this time, actually.
Ah.
Maybe I should consider Mayama.
Huh?
It's fine, I have a wide strike zone.
I'm totally down.
No, that's...
Sorry.
You should find someone else.
Huh?
Nah, I was totally joking.
Makes sense.
If your strike zone is that wide,
who else is there besides Mayama?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Do you work out, Asamiya?
No.
I just sprint to the station sometimes.
That's impressive.
Look at me, I'm just skin and bones.
I like you no matter how you look.
No, that's not it.
Wait.
Can you put your jacket on?
Huh?
But we're doing endurance
running today. I'll sweat.
Exactly.
Last time, your shirt
got a bit see-through.
But I didn't bring my track jacket today...
You can wear mine.
I can't let anyone else see.
Who would be happy
seeing my bare skin anyway?
I would.
I'll go on ahead.
Ah...
It smells like Asamiya.
What the hell am I thinking?
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven.
Maybe when Asamiya says he likes me,
it's just the kind of casual 'like'
popular guys throw around all the time.
Sakaki gave off the same vibe earlier.
Alright,
pair up and do some stretches.
Uh...
Mayama, are you flexible?
No.
I'm stiff. Super stiff.
Then I'll go easy on you.
Thanks.
Ow, ow, ow, ow! That hurts!
Were you lying just now?
Wait... I tap out, I tap out!
No tapping out.
I can't, I'm gonna split in half!
I'm seriously gonna split!
Wanna try pushing past your limits?
Ah... Wait!
Ow, wait a sec!
It hurts!
Switch.
What a shame.
Alright, I'm gonna push.
Yeah.
Is this the 'I'm not gonna cooperate' mode?
I'm already using all my strength.
Have you ever heard of karma?
Huh?
Wait, time out!
Seriously, stop for a sec!
You tortured me just now.
This is nothing.
Ah, sorry.
Huh?
Hey.
What are you two flirting about over there?
We got interrupted.
Shouldn't you take this run seriously?
I am running.
That's not what I meant.
Asamiya.
You can definitely run faster than this.
See?
Wait for me.
I'll lap you and come find you.
Hey, Mayama.
Have you and Asamiya
suddenly gotten super close lately?
Have we?
Because lately, Asamiya spends
more time with you than with us.
Honestly,
what do you think of Asamiya?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
He's just too far out of reach.
Out of reach, huh.
It's so hot.
Mayama, come here for a sec.
Asamiya said he has something to tell you.
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yeah...
I'm sorry.
I did something to upset you, didn't I?
You were mad just now, right?
I was.
Yeah, I was.
Even though I told you to wait for me...
Huh?
You ran off with Sakaki and the others.
Be more mindful next time.
Okay.
Um... okay?
Is this what you wanted
to talk to me about?
Wait, didn't you say
you wanted to talk to me?
Huh?
Oh crap, we're busted.
Ah, wait...
We'll leave you two alone.
If you feel like Asamiya is out of your league,
then just try harder to get closer to him.
What should we do?
They'll probably get bored of this soon.
You're way too calm about this.
Whoa.
Were you talking about
me being out of your league?
Well, how should I put this...
What's wrong?
I was sweating, and then the wind blew...
Mayama looks cold, Asamiya.
Warm him up.
It's fine. I'm used to this kind of thing.
Huh?
If we don't do this,
they'll never stop, right?
Do I still feel out of your league now?
You smell like Mayama.
People will get the wrong idea.
The wrong idea?
I mean...
You said you like me.
When you said you like me,
you meant as a friend, right?
You probably say that
to everyone else, too.
As if I would.
Alright, that's enough.
PDA time is over.
Did you get the shot?
Got it perfectly.
This is definitely getting
over ten thousand likes.
I'll kill you if you post that.
Just kidding.
We wouldn't actually do that.
I kinda want to post it, though.
I guess that's a no-go?
Our follower count would skyrocket.
Asamiya?
I'm sending it to my
phone before I delete it.
Why?
If you don't like it,
I'll delete it right away.
If you're just keeping it
for yourself, I guess it's fine.
Then I'll treat it as a family heirloom.
No, please don't.
Mayama.
Come here for a sec.
Huh?
Is this...
Am I about to get beaten up?
Because I got too close to Asamiya?
Listen.
We're sorry.
Huh?
Asamiya chewed us out after that.
He said we took the joke too far.
You see,
Asamiya,
he barely talks to anyone
other than us.
But he's opened up to you.
So we were really happy about it, too.
And we just got totally carried away.
We're sorry.
You don't have to apologize like that.
We want to be good friends with you, too.
Huh?
Don't just hang out with Asamiya.
Hang out with us, too.
No, someone like me...
Never mind.
Let's get along from now on.
Let's get along.
That's great.
Maybe we're the same.
Even though I arbitrarily labeled them
as the popular kids,
after talking to them like this,
I realized Sakaki and Tsunekawa
are just normal classmates.
I'm sure...
Do I still feel out of your league now?
I'm sure Asamiya is, too...
Asamiya.
You're hanging out with
those two behind my back again.
No, you've got it wrong.
This is...
Because we're friends.
Sakaki and Tsunekawa, too.
So isn't it normal for us all to get along?
I don't like being told
who I can be friends with.
I'm sorry.
Alright, I have a proposal.
It's about time to start prepping
for the cultural festival, right?
Mayama, you should be on
the planning committee with us.
The planning committee?
That's a great idea.
What do you say?
Asamiya, just the four of us.
Sounds good to me.
Awesome, then it's settled.
Great, let's go.
- Let's go.
- The planning committee, huh.
What does the planning committee do?
Whatever we want.
Like a maid cafe or something.
A maid cafe?
A maid cafe sounds good,
right? Everyone in maid outfits.
Asamiya in a maid outfit
would be a rare sight.
- I kinda want to see that.
- Hey.
- Then it's decided, maid outfits it is.
- It'd look cool.
- Everyone wants to see it.
- Any other ideas?
You don't hate it, do you?
Huh?
Being on the cultural
festival planning committee.
We didn't force you into it, did we?
It's fine.
You're always so worried
about that, Asamiya.
Always worrying if I hate something.
I'd rather die than do something you hate.
About hugging you on the balcony earlier...
If you hated it, I want to apologize.
I think it's really sweet of you.
I'm going this way.
See you tomorrow.
When Asamiya said he likes me,
he didn't mean it as a friend...
Does that mean I'll have to
give him a proper answer someday?
I don't dislike Asamiya.
Knowing he likes me actually makes me...
feel really happy.
But...
If I really had to give an answer,
that answer wouldn't be yes.
I'm really happy about your feelings.
But...
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Hey, hey.
Of course it was a joke.
As if anyone would actually like Mayama.
Yeah, right.
- He actually took it seriously.
- Are you for real?
Why would someone that cute
ever like you?
Stop flattering yourself.
Someone like me
is completely out of Asamiya's league.
Asamiya is probably just
having a momentary lapse in judgment.
(Next Episode Preview) Our class activity
for the cultural festival is a haunted house.
Could it be that you have someone you like?
We decided to have
Mayama play the werewolf.
So cute.
All done.
Did I scare you?
Why do I like him so much?
The only thing I know for sure is,
Mayama is my first love.
You're way too hard on yourself.
Mayama.
Here you go.
Huh?
It goes perfectly with the name Hare.
This is also a return gift.
Being told by Asamiya that he likes me...
I think I'm actually pretty happy about it.
Asamiya could definitely
find someone better.
I fell for you
because you're Mayama.